<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
             xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui">
    <ui:style>

    </ui:style>
    <g:HTMLPanel>


        <div style="display: inline-block;">
            <b>Exterior Incidences (in laws, sensibilities, parenting)</b>
            <br/>
        </div>
        <hr/>
        <span id="docs-internal-guid-57ea1dba-3e2e-cdf6-a76d-7354f670986d">
            <span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial; vertical-align: baseline; white-space: pre-wrap;"></span>
            <p dir="ltr" style="line-height:1.15;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;text-align: justify;">
                <span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial; vertical-align: baseline; white-space: pre-wrap;">The
                    exterior category deals with constructs formed outside the relationship in the past that are
                    relevant in the present and with constructs outside the relationship that affect it now.
                </span>
            </p>
            <p dir="ltr" style="line-height:1.15;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;text-align: justify;">
                <span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial; vertical-align: baseline; white-space: pre-wrap;">Such
                    constructs may be growing up with parents and acquiring some of their habits, the job with the boss,
                    the social circle and the raising of children.
                </span>
            </p>
            <br/>
            <span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial; vertical-align: baseline; white-space: pre-wrap;"></span>
            <p dir="ltr" style="line-height:1.15;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;text-align: justify;">
                <span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial; vertical-align: baseline; white-space: pre-wrap;">It
                    is important to note that the parenting of children is in this category. This is intentional as the
                    couple relationship may be deeply affected by children but it would be unwise to confuse couple
                    relationships with family relationships. Neither parents of the partners nor children should be
                    allowed to negatively affect or unbalance the couple while there is great benefit of them enriching
                    the couple.
                </span>
            </p>
            <br/>
            <span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial; vertical-align: baseline; white-space: pre-wrap;"></span>
            <p dir="ltr" style="line-height:1.15;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;text-align: justify;">
                <span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial; vertical-align: baseline; white-space: pre-wrap;">
                    <b>Joseph Burgo Phd - Why do I do that?</b>
                </span>
            </p>
            <p dir="ltr"
               style="line-height:1.15;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;margin-left: 36pt;text-align: justify;">
                <span style="font-size: 11px; font-family: Arial; vertical-align: baseline; white-space: pre-wrap;">
                    Generally speaking we all have sensibilities with their origins usually in our formative years all
                    the way through adolescence or any dramatic event during our lives. We need to understand our own
                    coping mechanisms when faced with negative emotions and endeavor to discuss them with and understand
                    our partners.
                </span>
            </p>
            <p dir="ltr"
               style="line-height:1.15;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;margin-left: 36pt;text-align: justify;">
                <span style="font-size: 11px; font-family: Arial; vertical-align: baseline; white-space: pre-wrap;">Why
                    Do I Do That? adapts the basic strategies of psycho-dynamic psychotherapy to a guided course in
                    self-exploration, highlighting the universal role of defense mechanisms in warding off emotional
                    pain. With easy-to-understand explanations, the first part teaches you about the unconscious mind
                    and the role of psychological defenses in excluding difficult feelings from awareness. Individual
                    chapters in the longer middle section explore the primary defense mechanisms one by one, with
                    exercises to help you identify your own defenses at work. The final part offers guidance for how to
                    "disarm" your defenses and cope more effectively with the unconscious feelings behind them.
                    Psychological defense mechanisms are an inevitable and necessary part of the human experience; but
                    when they become too pervasive or deeply entrenched, they may damage our personal relationships,
                    restrict or distort our emotional lives and prevent us from behaving in ways that promote lasting
                    self-esteem.
                </span>
            </p>
            <div>
                <span style="font-size: 11px; font-family: Arial; vertical-align: baseline; white-space: pre-wrap;">
                    <br/>
                </span>
            </div>
        </span>


    </g:HTMLPanel>
</ui:UiBinder>